<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Andrew Geisler</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Andrew Geisler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Education</title>
      <link>/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/education/</guid>
      <description>Middle Tennessee State University | Aug 2002 — Aug 2006  Bachelor of Science
Advertising | Marketing | Philosophy
  Datacamp.com  Data Scientist with R Track
 23 Courses Track completed April 2019  Big Data with R Track
 Introduction to Spark in R using sparklyr Parallel Programming in R Scalable Data Processing in R Writing Efficient R Code    Coursera.org   Bayesian Statistics: From Concept to Data Analysis Regression Models Statistical Inference    edx.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Examples</title>
      <link>/examples/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/examples/</guid>
      <description>GoodReads Github | Shiny App
 As an avid reader, Spotify&amp;rsquo;s Year in Review feature inspired me to see what I could learn from my own reading habits. I found that goodreads.com has an API where I could access my reading data. Analysis included year-over-year comparisons, reading pace, top genres, top authors, and sentiment analysis based on quotes from each books. Additionally, I learned that parsing XML is not for the faint of heart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experience</title>
      <link>/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/experience/</guid>
      <description>Freelance Data Analyst | May 2020 — Current  Providing support across a range of disciplines including data engineering, analysis, automation, and dashboard development.
 GoNoodle | May 2016 — May 2020 Senior Data Analyst  Supported product, marketing, and sales department goals by building models, custom analysis, and tools catered to specific business needs:
  Modeled user lifetime value based on potential ad revenue Modeled user engagement based on content consumption Survival analysis to address user retention goals A/B Testing (BayesAB) product features Projected and forecasted ad inventory and revenue opportunities Developed corporate dashboards to standardize business KPIs across the organization   Improved consistency and reliability of data products by designing and developing custom ETL data pipeline:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music</title>
      <link>/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/</guid>
      <description> Leaves EP Spotify | Apple Music | Google Play | Amazon
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>